<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on My Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on My Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/hero_carousel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/hero_carousel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi!   I&#39;m Vishwas.</title>
      <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 10:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/hero/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography I&amp;rsquo;m a Full stack Hardware design engineer. I work on things related to electronics, such as circuit designing, digital designing, Verilog coding, embedded coding, etc..yeah that&amp;rsquo;s what I do as a professional. As a hobbyist, I do much more than these things&amp;hellip;
As we all know necessity is the mother of invention, I strongly believe that we engineers, are here to solve real life problems not to create one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 10:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/skills/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/experience/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Posts</title>
      <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/posts/</guid>
      <description>Ham Radio Contest JULY - 2022 I participated in the annual HAM Radio competition here in Bengaluru and was able to make as many as 30 connections through the line of sight and repeater-assisted transmission. For the event, I used my homemade 4-element Yagi Antenna. I gave a talk on Edge AI - March 2022 I got an opportunity to give a talk on &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Edge AI&amp;rdquo; to 60+ 2nd Year Engineering Students of NIT AP, India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:42:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/projects/</guid>
      <description>LoRa based air quality monitor - 5 blogs A self sustained LoRa based Air Quality monitor using MKRWAN 1300 Smart Beehive monitoring systems Tele Vaidya - A remote health diagnosis sytem Opensource Vitals monitoring wearable UPS for WiFi Router NeoSense - Neonatal baby breath rate monitoring system Yes I Can - Interactive Teaching assistant for specially abled kids January 2020 - Current PyroLight - Smart attachemt for existing switch triggered by a Pyro Sensor January 2020 - Current Azure Smart Energy meter with IoT locker October 2019 - November 2019</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achievements</title>
      <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/achievements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:42:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/achievements/</guid>
      <description>Azure Devstories article contest My article Azure in Industrial IoT was selected as one of the top 20 articles among 80+ articles received for the competition.
Think ON Design Challenge by Element14.com and ON Semiconductor May 2020 Best Healthcare Application
Tranform your thinking by ON Semiconductor April 2020 Runner Up
Make sense of our proximity sense by kemet March 2020 Won 3rd Prize
Bring Intelligence to the Real world by Microsoft, Avnet, Octonian and Hackster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artworks</title>
      <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/artworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 01:42:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/artworks/</guid>
      <description> Elon Musk - June 2020 Pagoda - June 2020 Itomori from Kimi No Na Wa - May 2020 Radioactive - March 2020 Dacha - February 2020 I want some peace - November 2019 The beauty of nature - November 2019 Tribute to the Joker - October 2019 New York University - August 2019 I walk alone - June 2019 Tribute to Ironman - May 2019 Road to paradise - August 2018 Roof by the end of a cliff - July 2018 Tiger nest Monastery - July 2017 Paro bridge - March 2017 Long way ahead - September 2016 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 01:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vishwasnavada.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>